Maltese, Serphin R.; Papers apap382
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Constituent Case Files, 1990-2008; 3.6 cubic ft.
  - Doctorow, Jarvis, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Dodd, Lillian, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Doerge, Rosemarie, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Dojlidko, Dorothy, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Dolan, Marie, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Dolan, Patrick, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Dolce, Alfred, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Dollis, Peter, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Domanski, Margaret, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Dominick, Pauline, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Donnelly, Patricia, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Donnelly, William, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Donovan, Caroline, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Donovan, Lauren, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Donovan, Patrick, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Doran, Mary, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Douglas, Robert, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Douklowetzky, Lubov, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Dowd, John, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Doyle, Dennis, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Drasner, Mr., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Dreher, Charles, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Dreher, Helen, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Driscoll, Catherine, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Drobbin, Alice, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Droge, Ronald, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Drowne, John, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Drury, Peter, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Duarte, Patricia, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Ducas, Lillian, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Duenges, John, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - Duffy, William, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Duli, Peter, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Dulzer, Ernst, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Dumbach, Kevin, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Dunkelman, Arthur, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Dunn, Kenneth, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Dunne, Donald, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Dunning, Michelle, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Durocher, Jean, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Farina, Robert, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Fazio, Tom, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Fermin, Antonio, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Fink, Mathias, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Finley, Frank, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Finley, Lloyd, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Finn, Diana, Undated (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Finn, Margaret, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Finneran, Dennis, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Finneran, Olga, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Finnerty, Margaret, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Fiordimalva, Teresa, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - Firger, Eleanora, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - First Response Inc., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - Fischer, Arthur, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - Fischer, Gloria, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - Fish, Thomas, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - Fisher, Gerry, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - Fisher, Gloria, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - Fisher, Iris, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - Fisher, Joann, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - Fitzgerald, John, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - Fitzler, Caroline, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - Fitzpatrick, Margaret, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - Fiumano, Arlene, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - Flanagan, Hazel, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - Flanagan, Jim, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - Flezak, Mary, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 190)
  - Fling, Lorraine, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 191)
  - Flood, Dolores, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 192)
  - Flores, Alejandro, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 193)
  - Florio, Clem, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 194)
  - Flowers, Lorraine, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 195)
  - Fochetta, Jean, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 196)
  - Fogel, Amanda, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 197)
  - Foglino, Kathleen, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 198)
  - Foley, Brian, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 199)
  - Foley, Elenore, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 200)
  - Foley, Marion, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 201)
  - Ford, Alba, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 202)
  - Forest Hills Community House, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 203)
  - Forest Hills Volunteer Ambulance, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 204)
  - Forgione, Michelina, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 205)
  - Forst, Mary, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 206)
  - Forste, Marvin, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 207)
  - Forte, Cathy, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 208)
  - Forte, Dominick and Bernadette, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 209)
  - Forte, John, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 210)
  - Forte, Virginia, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 211)
  - Fortuna, Leonard F., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 212)
  - Fortunato, Dominick, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 213)
  - Forzano, Claire, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 214)
  - Fostel, Lucille, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 215)
  - Foster, Deborah, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 216)
  - Fowley, Edward, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 217)
  - Fox, Alice, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 218)
  - Fox, Margaret, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 219)
  - Francin, Rudy, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 220)
  - Francisco, Leslie, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 221)
  - Franco, Isabel, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 222)
  - Frandina, Amedeo, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 223)
  - Frank, Alice, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 224)
  - Frank, Ira, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 225)
  - Frank, Samuel, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 226)
  - Frankel, Ilona C., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 227)
  - Frankhouser, Mack, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 228)
  - Franz, Helmut, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 229)
  - Franz, Mr., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 230)
  - Franzem, Jeanette, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 231)
  - Franzese, Fred, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 232)
  - Franzke, Alois P., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 233)
  - Fraser, Simone, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 234)
  - Frazia, Al, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 235)
  - Frazia, Josephine, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 236)
  - Frazier, George, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 237)
  - Freda, Arthur, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 238)
  - Freedman, Joel, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 239)
  - French-Yee, Kathleen, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 240)
  - Frey, Francis, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 241)
  - Frey, Lida, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 242)
  - Friedberg, Howard, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 243)
  - Friedgood, Charles, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 244)
  - Friedman, Florence, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 245)
  - Friedrich, Dorothy, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 246)
  - Frier, Francis, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 247)
  - Friesing, Amelia, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 248)
  - Frigano, Michael, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Frisbie, Lisa, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Frisbie, William, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Fruechtnicht, Virginia, 1994; 2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fruth, Rosalyn, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Fugazy, William Denis, 1992; 1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Fulcher, Margaret, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Fullam, Charlene, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Fumei, Joseph, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Funari, Anthony, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Fuoco, Anthony, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Furey, Frank, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Furey, Jane Loughlin, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Furino, Gloria, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Furst, Robert, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Fusaro, Mary, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Fusco, Assunta, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Gray, William, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Greater Woodhaven Development Corporation, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Greene, Lewis and Frances, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Gregg, Charles, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Gregg, Tommy, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Guarino, Anna, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Guarino, Cynthia, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Guarrella, George, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Gulotta, Anthony, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Gundy, Debbie, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Hanson, Ivylyn, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Harrison, Catherine, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Heineman, Marc, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Heinemann, Antoinette, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Heinsch, Dolores, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Heinsohn, Edmund, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Heinson, William, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Heinstadt, Dorothy, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Heinz, May, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Heiter, Jack, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Helferich, Charles, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Heller, Sanford, 1991; 1993 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Helmstadt, Gerard, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Henderson, Janice, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Henley, Rosalie, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Hentschel, Agnes, 1990; 1994 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Herrmann, Agnes, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Hershkowitz, Victor, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Hertler, Marion, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Hetzer, Michael, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Heubner, Arthur, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Hewko, Christina, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Hickey, Lorraine, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Hickey, Peter, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Higgins, Jimmy, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Hillmeyer, Ida, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Himrod Street Residents, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Hiotis, Stelios, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Hiralall, Bibi, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Hobbs, William, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Hochwald, Richard, 1993; 1996 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Hoffman, Bob, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Hoffman, Eileen, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Hoffman, James, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Hoffman, John, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Hofler, Bob, 1994; 1996 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Hogan, John, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Horn, Lori Ann, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Horvath, Joe, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Hounsell, Jack, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Howard Beach Senior Center, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Howard, Janet, 1993; 1995 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Hua, Xiang, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Huang, Maryanne, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Hubert, Johanna, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Huey, Lillie, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Hughes, David, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Huneke, George P., 2003 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Hunter, Jenny, Undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Hurley, Margaret, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Hurst, Margaret, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Hurto, Joseph, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Hutchinson, George, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Hutchinson, Kenneth, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Hyjek, Helen, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Hynes, John, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Iavarone, Ferdinand, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Illes, Frank, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Innamorata, Lori-Ann, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Insogna, Frances, Undated (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Iovino, Carmine, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Irmscher, Eleanor, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Ittem, Peter, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Jabar, Abdool and Bibi, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Jaccino, Dora, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Jacina, Peter, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Jacob, Craig, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Jacobowitz, Joyce, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Jadduroy, Dianand, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Jamoona, Chan, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Janssen, Ronald, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Jarmek, Theodore, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Javna, Jonas, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Jednyak, Jacek, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Jenkus, Eva, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - John Adams High School PTA, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Joyce, John, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Joyce, Robert, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Kaiser, Jacqueline, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Kamrul, Mohammed, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Karnbach, Margaret, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Karpowicz, Michelle, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Kava, Terri, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Kava, William J., 1999 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Kaveney, Jerome, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Kazas, Paul Michael, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Kellner, Elizabeth, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Kenny, Kathleen, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Kercoban, Olga, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Kern, Mary Ann, Undated (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Kessler, William, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Khemlani, Gulu, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Kiefer, Lily, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Kikta, Anastasia, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Kircher, Margaret, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Kirschner, Dr. Howard Jay, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Klein, Sigmund, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Knack, William, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Knett, Cathy, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Knoblock, John, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Kobleck, Gus, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Koch, Bob, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Koenig, Frank, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Kohlheb, Elizabeth, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Kolenovic, Enisa, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Konopka, Nadine, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Koppel, Ronald, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Kornichuk, Janette, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Kosovic, Laza, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Kotas, Teresa, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Kozicki, Gerald, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Krasowski, William, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Kreider, Terence, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Krolik, Eugenia, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Kruithoff, Dennis, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Kung, Nancy, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Kunkel, Geraldine, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - La Rosa, Donna, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - LaCova, Jaqueline, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Langone, Debbie, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Laura, Maxine, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Lavin, Myrtle and James, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Lebland, Pauline, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Lee, Lester, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Leudesdorf, Arthur, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Levins, Etta, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Levy, Eileen, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Lew, Claire, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Lewandowski, Violet, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Lewis, Jeffrey, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Liberatore, Elizabeth, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Lingan, Gency, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Lissner, Eileen, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - LoCascio, Joseph, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Lombardi, Vinnie, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Lombardo, Salvatore, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Long, Harvey, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Lowry, John, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Lucas, Ted, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Luizza, Theresa, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Lupo, Guy, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Lupuku, Lama, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - M, Mr. G, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Madigan, Herbert, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Magno, Teresa, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Malik, Jorge, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - Maltese, Frank, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Mandala, Catherine, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Manea, Elena, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - Mangiaracina, Lillian, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - Maniace, Elizabeth, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - Maniscalco, Frank, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - Mansuto, Simon, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - Manus, Evelyn, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 181)
  - Martin, Joseph, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 182)
  - McEvoy, Thomas, 1993; 1996 (Box 2, Folder 183)
  - McEvoy, Veronica, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 184)
  - McGinnis, John, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 185)
  - McGowan, Lawrence, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 186)
  - McGowan, William, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 187)
  - McGrane, Toni, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 188)
  - McGrath, Diane, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 189)
  - McGuiness, John, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 190)
  - McGuinness, Elizabeth, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 191)
  - McGuire, Carolyn, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 192)
  - McKeegan, Kevin, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 193)
  - McKeel, Kenneth, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 194)
  - McKeeves, Sue, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 195)
  - McKenna, Gloria, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 196)
  - McKenzie, Janice, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 197)
  - McKeon, Elizabeth, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 198)
  - McKeough, Joyce, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 199)
  - McKewen, Howard, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 200)
  - McKiernan, Francis, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 201)
  - McKuhan, George, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 202)
  - McLaren, Helen, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 203)
  - McLaughlin, Cheryl/Sheryl, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 204)
  - McLaughlin, Mary, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 205)
  - McLaughlin, Myrtle, 1992; 1995 (Box 2, Folder 206)
  - McLaughlin, William, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 207)
  - McLean, Ruth, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 208)
  - McLeod, Roslyn, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 209)
  - McMahon, Bryan, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 210)
  - McMahon, Elizabeth, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 211)
  - McMahon, Matthew, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 212)
  - McMahon, Robert, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 213)
  - McManus, Elizabeth, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 214)
  - McManus, Michelle, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 215)
  - McNally, Anne, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 216)
  - McNamara, Edward, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 217)
  - McNamara, Michael R., 1992 (Box 2, Folder 218)
  - McNulty, James and Pat, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 219)
  - McPartland, Patrick, Undated (Box 2, Folder 220)
  - McSkimming, Mildred, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 221)
  - Mead, Linda, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 222)
  - Mead, Robert, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 223)
  - Meaney, Antoinette, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 224)
  - Meaney, Jacqueline, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 225)
  - Meany, Raymond, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 226)
  - Mechow, Robert, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 227)
  - Medaglia, Marie, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 228)
  - Medez, Albert, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 229)
  - Medina, Janet, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 230)
  - Meditz, Harold, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 231)
  - Meditz, Richard, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 232)
  - Meehan, Helen, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 233)
  - Meehan, John, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 234)
  - Meehan, Monica, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 235)
  - Meeks, Gregory, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 236)
  - Mehling, John and Madeline, 1991; 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 237)
  - Mehling, Richard, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 238)
  - Meidenbauer, Frank, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 239)
  - Meinck, Irene, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 240)
  - Mejia, Teresa, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 241)
  - Melendez, Carlos, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 242)
  - Melendez, Carmen, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 243)
  - Melendez, Danny, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 244)
  - Melendez, Migdalia, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 245)
  - Meli, Francesca, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 246)
  - Melzak, Bennett, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 247)
  - Memolo, Frank, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 248)
  - Mendelson, Judith, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 249)
  - Mendolia, Suzanne, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 250)
  - Mendoza, Iris, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 251)
  - Mendoza, Luz, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 252)
  - Mengler, Edgar, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 253)
  - Menis, Angelo, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 254)
  - Menk, Rita, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 255)
  - Menna, Thomas, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 256)
  - Menogiano, Hilda, Undated (Box 2, Folder 257)
  - Menzel, Gertrude, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Menzies, Christopher, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Mercogliano, Hilda, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Merenda, Salvatore, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Meri, Luke, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Merkel, Loraine, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Merlo, Rose, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Merola, Andrew, 1990; 1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Meroni, Donna, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Merrett, Alfred, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Merry, Rosemarie, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Mesk, Sandy, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Messana, Giuseppi, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Messina, Camille, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Messina, Giovanni, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Messina, Jack, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Messina, Patricia, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Messina, Stephen, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Metta, Daniel (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Metzing, Theodore, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Metzler, Emma, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Metzler, Fran, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Meyer, Augusta, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Meyer, Lothar, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Meyer, Ruth, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Meyer, Walter, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Meyers, George, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Mezack, Robert, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Mezher, Sawson and Nabil, 1993; 1996 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Micale, Carmelina, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Micale, Guitano, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Michaelis, Roseanne, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Michalski, Paul, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Mickaelis, George, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Micozzi, Anthony, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Micozzi, Ronald, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Middle Village Volunteer Ambulance Corps, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Middleton, Lillian, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Middleton, Norma, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Miele, Antonio, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Miele, Mary, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Migliaccio, Anthony, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Migliaccio, Arnold, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Migliaccio, Blanche, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Mignardi, Virgilia, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Mignone, Mary, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Mignone, Theresa, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Mihaila-Greceanu, Ioana, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Mikol, Irene, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Miles, Arthur, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Milewczik, John, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Miller, Catherine, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Miller, Olympia, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Minichino, Pauline, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Mizzi, Mrs., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Moceli, Vito, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Nacabuan, Romualdo, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Nagel, Florence, 1991; 1993; 1997 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Naglieri, Sam, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Nandkishore, Rosy Anna, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Naples, Louise, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Napoli, John, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Napoli, Lina, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Napoli, Mark, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Napoli, Shelley, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Napolitano, Vincent, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Nappi, Lucille, 1993; 1995 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Nappi, Maria, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Nappo, Jerry, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Naraine, Steve, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Nardella, Robert, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Nardi, Anthony, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Nardin, Cynthia, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Narducci, Vito, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Naseck, Pauline, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Nash, Catherine, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Nash, Josh, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Nashak, Robert, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Nasher, Waleed, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Naso, Mr., 1995 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Nathan, Stephen, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Natole, Raymond, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Natyna, Bondanna, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Nawmann, Eric, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Naylor, Margaret, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Neary, Dorothy, 1995; 1999 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Negoe, Adrianna, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Negrette, Fernando, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Negron, Delphin, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Neidhardt, Joe, 1991; 1999 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Neir, Lidya, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Nelson, Edward, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Nelson, Joseph, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Nemeth, Catherine, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Nemoga, Joyce, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Nerlich, Ella, 1994; 1999 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Neuhaus, Nick, 1995; 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Neumann, John, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Newman, Caroline, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Nicita, Theresa, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Nicola, Alfonso, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Nicollet, George, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Nicoloudis, Michael, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Nielson-Sallois, Karen, 1993; 1997 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Nobel, Mary, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Nolan, Agnes, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Nolan, George (Mrs.), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Nunez, Daniel, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Occhiuto, Joe, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - O'Malley, Jerry, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Onestuk, Julie Ann, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Palermo, Angela, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Pampalone, JoAnn, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Pannacchione, Barbara, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Pappas, Maura, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Pappas, Olga, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Paraskos, Agnes, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Passaillo, Vito, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Passudeppi, Donald, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Pasterzy, Phylis, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Paugh, Mervin, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Pazos, Dennis, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Peck, Alfred, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Peglow, Helen, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Pepe, Michael, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Pepi, Stella, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Peppel, Kevin, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Perfaud, Rhoda, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Persaued, Dheni, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Perun, Stephen, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Peters, Gary, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 131)